OSCAR SANZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

After more than 15 years of experience in hospitality and tourism, I decided to pursue a career in software development. The adaptability I gained through working in different jobs and countries (Russia and England) enabled me to complete a Full Stack Development bootcamp and learn more quickly and efficiently.

My experience in positions of responsibility has enabled me to develop my organizational and communication abilities.

LANGUAGES

Spanish: native English: B2

TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript React
MERN PostgreSQL
Node.is Docker

HTML5 AWS

CSS3 Styled-Compoents

SaSS Tailwind CSS

Typescript

CONTACT INFO

Mobile: 625 68 00 02 osanzce@gmail.com Madrid

GitHub

Linkedin

Web

PROJECTS

Personal Projects

Full Stack Developer / Jun 2021 - Present

Social-face

React Node.js Express MongoDB Socket.IO Redux React-Hooks

It is a Facebook-inspired social network that allows users to tag contacts in addition to following them and publishing content with photos. It also has an **online chat** via **web sockets**. Sessions and cookies are implemented to manage authentication. The front-end is deployed on **Netlify** and the back-end on **Render**. User y password for demo: john@doe.com / 1234

<u>Demo</u> <u>Front-end</u> <u>Back-end</u>

Jobfindr

React Node.js Express PostgreSQL JWT Nodemailer Puppeteer

A **web scraper** that searches for jobs posted on a job board using keywords. **JWT** is used for authentication management. The application sends a daily email to the specified email account at the time determined by a **cron job** containing information about new jobs added to the database in the previous 24 hours. The application is hosted on **AWS EC2** and has an **SSL** certificate.

User and password for demo guest@guest.com / guest

Demo Code

Smart-Brain

React Node.js Express MongoDB Typescript Docker React-Context

A **facial recognition** application that frames the faces in a user-supplied photo. The application includes a counter that displays the number of photos uploaded by the user. **Sessions and cookies** are applied to manage authentication. **Tailwind CSS** is used to create the app's styles, and **Typescript** is used to create the backend. The app is currently being developed in a **Docker** container.

Code

FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA

Upgrade-Hub

Full stack developer / Nov 2020 - May 2021

Universidad Camilo J. Cela

Internatioanal Marketing Master / Oct 2012 - Jun2013

Universidad de Valencia

Bachelor's Degreee in Tourism / Sep 2003 - Jul 2017

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Kahelar Group

Shift Manager / Jul 2013 - Present

Playboy Club London

Chef / Apr 2011 - Aug 2012

Spanish Tourims Office in Embassy of Spain in Moscow

Junior Marketing Representative / May 2008 - Aug 2010